[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what 1987 horror movie does this conversation occur:\n-Wait a minute, who am I here?\n-Jerry?\n-Thats right. Jerry Blake. Thanks, honey.?", "correct_answer": "The Stepfather", "incorrect_answers": ["Brain Damage", "Shocker", "American Gothic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Meryl Streeps performance in this 1982 movie brought her her first Academy Award for Best Actress.", "correct_answer": "Sophies Choice", "incorrect_answers": ["Silkwood", "Kramer vs. Kramer", "Out of Africa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which employee from the movie Office Space was not fired or laid off?", "correct_answer": "Peter", "incorrect_answers": ["Milton", "Tom", "Samir"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these inhabited places is wettest?", "correct_answer": "Moulein", "incorrect_answers": ["Sylhet", "Baguio", "Lae"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The original Saw movie was shot in 18 days.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was drafted by the Houston Rockets in the first overall selection of the 1984 NBA draft?", "correct_answer": "Hakeem Olajuwon", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Jordan", "John Stockton", "Charles Barkley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a corkscrew-shaped pasta?", "correct_answer": "farfalle", "incorrect_answers": ["cavatappi", "rotini", "fusilli"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the ending credits of the movie Animal House, Boon and Katy got married in 1964 and divorced in what year?", "correct_answer": "1969", "incorrect_answers": ["1967", "1965", "1971"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the Iguazu Falls, located in South America, mean in English?", "correct_answer": "Big water", "incorrect_answers": ["Way to heaven", "River storm", "Devils waterfall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The bride traditionally wears a veil, because it is considered bad luck for the groom to see the bride before the wedding.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the original name of the melodramatic musical, West Side Story?", "correct_answer": "East Side Story", "incorrect_answers": ["War and Love", "The Gangs of New York", "Jets and Sharks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Literally translated Feng Shui means wind and water.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]